foreign
hey guys welcome back to off grid
we have a special video planned for you
um but before we get started in this big
little mini Beauty thing on the table
you need to get signed up for our
permanent care class next one is March
25th you can sign up for that on our
website which is off-gridarmory.us also
you sign for the class but also make
sure you share this video with everybody
in your friends list on Facebook because
Facebook is Banning the crap out of us
okay nobody sees any of our videos
anymore so share them also want to give
a shout out to mark from St Louis who
called this morning and said hey we love
the videos and we shut the uh our
workplace down every time you put out a
video and we put your videos on the big
screen and everybody stops working and
we watch the video so mark from St Louis
this video is for you
who needs a mini 50 in your life I
posted a picture of this on Facebook
last night tons of people were like oh
my gosh where can I get one send me a
link I want to buy that right now
guys we sell these
okay I literally sell these
this is the Noreen mini 50. this is a
Noreen URL
chambered in 50 BMG it isn't exactly 16
inch barrel
comes with this
solid aluminum little slide on buttstock
it's actually attached to a Pickney rail
back here but this is a brand new
product from Noreen they actually built
this as a joke
so
the company is well known for building
single shot 50s and they built it as a
joke they built the shortest smallest
most compact 50 ever
they put
online and they started selling like
hotcakes like they invented this by
accident
and that's where I saw it I saw it
online reached out to the company we
were already a Noreen dealer and I was
like man I need those pistols in my life
so this is basically a product review of
the Noreen Mini 50. so this guy weighs
in at 18 pounds
this is an 18 pound it's technically a
rifle but it's a pistol
um kind of confusing but this break on
here is gnarly it's humongous it does
not come with the installed bipod I
actually robbed this off another gun
here at off-grid but this is a Barrett
Atlas bipod these run about three
hundred dollars there weren't too many
bipods that I would trust for shooting
on something like this I'm pretty sure
any bipod you put on
this rifle other than a Barrett Atlas is
probably gonna just explode just shred
or bend or just snap off the gun so I
put on the heaviest Duty bipod I had in
stock and then I wanted to go the
opposite direction so you could run a
scope or a little red dot on this thing
I'm actually running a 189 dollar
Hawk
Circle Dot
it's just a little reflex dock it's 189
dollars it's super cool
we're a hawk dealer and I just I'm gonna
be shooting at a Target like 75 feet
away so why would I put a three to nine
by 56 on this thing or a 4 to 12 by 56
it doesn't make sense so I just threw a
little red dot on here like I said this
is a single shot bolt
so a lot of people in the post yesterday
they were like man let's I want to see
you shoot this thing honestly all of us
here at off grid are a little terrified
to shoot this gun so if you've shot a 50
before do you remember when you shot the
Barrett x95 the little Bullpup with that
huge Crown break on there it had a 20
inch barrel on it so it was really close
to your face what did it feel like when
you shot the Barrett x95
garbage it hurts so bad yeah it felt
like a nosebleed like an instant
nosebleed
I'm terrified of this gun
but I can't sell it if I've never shot
one before so I'm gonna go outside I'm
gonna put I'm gonna try to shoot twice
Blake's gonna try to shoot it twice and
then Grant might shoot it we'll see
he'll probably be terrified but I'm
gonna grab two Blake you're gonna take
two and we're gonna try we're gonna
attempt to put four rounds through this
thing I don't know how it's gonna go it
is gonna
it is I am gonna wear double ear Pro
and Blake only has one set of ear Pro
or whatever you got to take care of
yourself first right
double ear Pro here we go so I'm all set
there
oh this thing is such a chunk
such a beautiful little chunk oh I
forgot to mention how much is it
16.49
without the Red Dot or bipod
like I said that little guy is about 299
this is only 189 dollars
so I have two of these available if you
want one
give us a shout our numbers 218-657-2264
here we go like I said single shot bolt
Slide the bolts out
Trace around this is Lake City Ammo
yep League City from
1970 1997.
okay snapping you around just like that
feed her up in there
lock it in place
are you sure we don't have any customers
in the store right now
because the door is open yeah you should
go shut that yeah just in case I would
shut that door
imagine being in the store and hearing
this while you're trying to buy AR-15
parts without knowing what's going on
outside exactly
so the one drawback to this aluminum
butt stock no padding
okay I have a titanium shoulder
this is a titanium shoulder long story
but we're about to find out how this is
okay what should I shoot at Blake one of
those gongs you want to shoot still
the 50.
I sort of feel like why not
let's do it all right
you only live once right
all right there we go
got my Red Dot on
you ready for this
foreign
I'm scared oh come on I'm scared are you
ready
don't drop the camera
all right here we go make sure your
mouth is open by the way okay
three two
one
oh my God
look at my face
did you see that
look at your sweatshirt did you see that
the amount of snow that came up with oh
it's still swinging
oh that was dope I want to do that again
so
it didn't hurt no it was just everything
that just blew up around
but I gotta do that again
so you just pop it out
pop out your spent showcase oh my gosh
this thing is stupid
could you see the Tracer
no I think your eyes are shut your eyes
were shut
oh my gosh
um I lost my price tag
I don't know where that went man this
thing is awesome
feed it in lock it down
pack in place
so after I pull the trigger I couldn't
see a thing it was just white out
all right going for the big one this
time
three
two
one
oh man I am in love
I am going to shoot a deer with this
this deer season
oh my Lord have mercy
bipad is still intact
its world has been rocked slightly
I lost uh one of the leg positions there
we go now she's equal on both sides
Blake
you were up my friend
all right let's switch places I want to
see what it's like on the bystander side
oh man
that thing okay so my shoulder does hurt
just a little bit
just a little
I can't imagine why
yep it is a positive lock so once it's
in place
dude are you going to stand and shoot it
did I no yes yes
stand and shoot it
oh this is gonna suck for me
oh
all right Brave man here we go
three two one
oh
wow
that is I think I need one of these oh
that is the that is probably perhaps the
most recoil I've ever felt ever shooting
anything
there goes that round he's jonesing for
another one you know it
yep that's called the uh you got the
shakes
now I want more
standing again
three two one
oh my gosh yeah look at that gong swing
oh
yeah thumbs up or thumbs down
this thing is amazing that thing is the
coolest
I have to say that's probably the
coolest 50 I've ever shot I would have
to agree this thing is
it's just straight up gnarly it is
there she is guys
Noreen
ulr 50 the mini 50 come on down to off
grid and pick up one today
see you guys